Guide to the Antiquarian bookseller catalog collection.
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- J
  - X346 J961 IV, undated, 1955-1965; nos. 18-40, 10 lists
    - W. Junk; Berlin (Box 878, Folder 5653)
  - X346 J961 V, undated, 1957-1973; nos. 8-86, unnumbered, 19 catalogs
    - W. Junk; Berlin (Box 878, Folder 5654)
    - W. Junk; Berlin (Box 879, Folder 5655-5656)
- K
  - X346 K124, undated; nos. 12-121, 10 catalogs
    - Gunnar A. Kaldewey; München (Box 879, Folder 5657-5659)
  - X346 K128, undated; nos. 1-48, 26 catalogs
    - Kamin Bookshop; New York City (Box 879, Folder 5660)
    - Kamin Bookshop; New York City (Box 880, Folder 5661)
  - X346 K1286, 1957-1968; nos. 1-47, 18 catalogs
    - Victor Kamkin, Inc.; Washington, D.C. (Box 880, Folder 5662-5663)
  - X346 K1413, undated; nos. 5-31, 5 catalogs
    - Carolyn Kaplan; Laguna Beach, California (Box 880, Folder 5664-5665)
  - X346 K1415, 1961-1970, undated; nos. 3-27, 8 catalogs
    - Boris Kaplanski; Paris, France (Box 880, Folder 5666)
  - X346 K146, 1924-1939; nos. 13-74, 14 catalogs
    - Karl Faber; München (Box 880, Folder 5667)
    - Karl Faber; München (Box 881, Folder 5668-5670)
  - X346 K1461, 1968; no. 114, 1 catalog
    - Karl u. Faber; München (Box 881, Folder 5671)
  - X346 K24, 1892; unnumbered, 1 catalog
    - Keelar, Davis Co.; 110 Montgomery Street (Box 881, Folder 5672)
  - X346 K259, 1939-1977; nos. 1-92, 8 catalogs
    - Kegan Paul, Trench Trubner LTD.; London (Box 881, Folder 5673)
  - X346 K259 II, 1892-1904; nos. 2-13, 12 catalogs
    - Kegan Paul, Trench Trubner LTD.; London (Box 882, Folder 5674-5675)
  - X346 K259 III, 1915-1954; nos. 1-48, 36 catalogs
    - Kegan Paul, Trench Trubner LTD.; London (Box 882, Folder 5676-5678)
    - Kegan Paul, Trench Trubner LTD.; London (Box 883, Folder 5679-5681)
  - X346 K259 IV, undated; nos. 1-4, 4 catalogs
    - Kegan Paul, Trench Trubner LTD.; London (Box 883, Folder 5682)
  - X346 K259 V, 1933-1937, undated; unnumbered, 13 catalogs
    - Kegan Paul, Trench Trubner LTD.; London (Box 883, Folder 5683-5684)
  - X346 K259 VI, 1954-undated; nos. 49-96, 30 catalogs
    - Kegan Paul, Trench Trubner LTD.; London (Box 884, Folder 5685-5690)
  - X346 K259 VII, 1940; no. 1, 1 catalog
    - Kegan Paul, Trench Trubner LTD.; London (Box 885, Folder 5691)
  - X346 K28, undated; nos. 151-169, 11 catalogs
    - Wm. F. Kelleher; Cliffside Park, N. J. (Box 885, Folder 5692-5693)
  - X346 K297, undated; no. 5, 1 catalog
    - W. B. Kelly; Dublin (Box 885, Folder 5694)
  - X346 K31, 1954-1958; nos. 2-11, 8 catalogs
    - Kelley Millman, Inc.; New York, New York (Box 885, Folder 5695-5696)
  - X346 K363 II, 1921-1948; nos. 4-29, 23 catalogs
    - T. M. Kennard; England (Box 885, Folder 5697-5698)
  - X346 K3992, undated; nos. 2-46, 11 catalogs
    - Kenny's Bookshops; Galway (Box 886, Folder 5699-5701)
  - X346 K446, 1891-1911; no. 8, unnumbered, 5 catalogs
    - Frederick Keppel Co.; New York, New York (Box 886, Folder 5702-5704)
  - X346 K461, undated-1959; nos. 5-84, 28 catalogs
    - Ewen Kerr; Kendal, Westmorland (Box 887, Folder 5705)
  - X346 K47, undated; nos. 136-143, 5 catalogs
    - M. Kershner; New York, New York (Box 887, Folder 5706)
  - X346 K475, 1857-1875; unnumbered, 2 catalogs
    - Thomas Kerslake; Bristol (Box 887, Folder 5707)
  - X346 K475 II, undated, 1845; nos. 1-10, 10 catalogs
    - Thomas Kerslake; Bristol (Box 887, Folder 5708-5709)
  - X346 K494, undated; nos. 1-14, 15 catalogs
    - Fred G. Ketcheson; Toronto, Canada (Box 887, Folder 5710-5711)
  - X346 K495, undated; nos. 1-6, 6 catalogs
    - R. N. Ketterer; Switzerland (Box 888, Folder 5712-5717)
  - X346 K5423, undated; nos. 116-124, 9 catalogs
    - Rene Kieffer; Paris (Box 888, Folder 5718)
  - X346 K572, 1907-1940; nos. 125-239, 50 catalogs
    - Henry Kimpton; London (Box 889, Folder 5719-5720)
  - X346 K572 II, 1855-1857; unnumbered, 4 catalogs
    - Henry Kimpton; London (Box 889, Folder 5721)
  - X346 K573, 1855; nos. 40-42, 2 catalogs
    - Richard Kimpton; Soho (Box 889, Folder 5722)
  - X346 K574, undated; nos. 1-6, 5 catalogs
    - Clifford E. King; London (Box 889, Folder 5723)
  - X346 K575, 1888-1940; nos.182-605, 201 catalogs
    Includes some unnumbered catalogs
    - P.S. King Son; Westminster (Box 889, Folder 5724-5726)
    - P.S. King Son; Westminster (Box 890, Folder 5727-5731)
  - X346 K577, undated; nos. 3-13, 7 catalogs
    - Patrick King LTD; Stony Stratford (Box 891, Folder 5732)
  - X346 K58, 1927-1950, undated; nos. 1-57, 56 catalogs
    - Raphael King; London (Box 891, Folder 5733-5736)
    - Raphael King; London (Box 892, Folder 5737-5738)
  - X346 K58 I, undated; unnumbered, 1 catalog
    - Raphael King; London (Box 892, Folder 5739)
  - X346 K5871, 1812; unnumbered, 1 catalog
    - Thos. King; London (Box 892, Folder 5740)
  - X346 K618, undated; nos. 1-37, 35 catalogs
    - Kingston Gallaries, Inc.; Boston (Box 892, Folder 5741-5744)
    - Kingston Gallaries, Inc.; Boston (Box 893, Folder 5745-5746)
  - X346 K635, 1951, undated; nos. 1-19, 11 catalogs
    - Kirgo's; New Haven, CT (Box 893, Folder 5747)
  - X346 K676, 1871-1955; nos. 1-223, 67 catalogs
    - Klemmings Antiqvariat; Stockholm (Box 893, Folder 5748-5750)
    - Klemmings Antiqvariat; Stockholm (Box 894, Folder 5751-5755)
    - Klemmings Antiqvariat; Stockholm (Box 895, Folder 5756)
  - X346 K685, 1924-1957; unnumbered, 8 catalogs
    - C. Klincksieck; Paris (Box 895, Folder 5757)
  - X346 K695, undated; nos. 10-40, 22 catalogs
    - D. Klokatcheff; Roma (Box 895, Folder 5758-5759)
  - X346 K74, 1827; unnumbered, 1 catalog
    - Knibb and Langbridge; Worchester (Box 895, Folder 5760)
  - X346 K761, 1897; nos. 26-31, 2 catalogs
    - John H. Knowles; London (Box 895, Folder 5761)
  - X346 K762, 1927-1938; nos. 1-25, 15 catalogs
    - John H. Knowles; London (Box 896, Folder 5762)
  - X346 K7995, undated; nos. 30-34, 5 catalogs
    - Kobunso; Tokyo, Japan (Box 896, Folder 5763-5765)
  - X346 K818, 1888-1893, undated; nos. 1-29, 19 catalogs
    - K. F. Koehler; Leipzig (Box 896, Folder 5766-5767)
    - K. F. Koehler; Leipzig (Box 897, Folder 5768)
  - X346 K818 I, undated, 1925-1927; unnumbered, 15 catalogs
    - K. F. Koehler; Leipzig (Box 897, Folder 5769-5772)
  - X346 K818 II, 1860-1912; nos. 56-589, 353 catalogs
    - K. F. Koehler; Leipzig (Box 898, Folder 5773-5778)
    - K. F. Koehler; Leipzig (Box 899, Folder 5779-5784)
    - K. F. Koehler; Leipzig (Box 900, Folder 5785-5790)
    - K. F. Koehler; Leipzig (Box 901, Folder 5791-5796)
    - K. F. Koehler; Leipzig (Box 902, Folder 5797-5802)
    - K. F. Koehler; Leipzig (Box 903, Folder 5803-5808)
    - K. F. Koehler; Leipzig (Box 904, Folder 5809-5814)
    - K. F. Koehler; Leipzig (Box 905, Folder 5815-5820)
    - K. F. Koehler; Leipzig (Box 906, Folder 5821-5827)
    - K. F. Koehler; Leipzig (Box 907, Folder 5828-5833)
    - K. F. Koehler; Leipzig (Box 908, Folder 5834)
  - X346 K818 III, 1913-1940; nos. 1-128, 68 catalogs
    - K. F. Koehler; Leipzig (Box 908, Folder 5835-5838)
    - K. F. Koehler; Leipzig (Box 909, Folder 5839-5843)
    - K. F. Koehler; Leipzig (Box 910, Folder 5844-5848)
    - K. F. Koehler; Leipzig (Box 911, Folder 5849-5853)
  - X346 K818 IV, 1926-undated; nos. 2-110, 29 catalogs
    - K. F. Koehler; Leipzig (Box 911, Folder 5854)
    - K. F. Koehler; Leipzig (Box 912, Folder 5855-5859)
  - X346 K819, 1930-1939; nos. 43-47, 5 catalogs
    - Paul Koehler; Leipzig (Box 912, Folder 5860)
    - Paul Koehler; Leipzig (Box 913, Folder 5861-5865)
    - Paul Koehler; Leipzig (Box 914, Folder 5866-5868)
  - X346 K8191, 1955-1968; nos. 176-213, 23 catalogs
    - Otto Koeltz; Koenigstein, West Germany (Box 914, Folder 5869-5871)
    - Otto Koeltz; Koenigstein, West Germany (Box 915, Folder 5872)
  - X346 K8192, undated; nos. 5-12, 8 catalogs
    - Josef Kosel; München (Box 915, Folder 5873)
  - X346 K8242, 1968-1985; nos. 1-15, 14 catalogs
    - C. C. Kohler; Surrey, England (Box 915, Folder 5874-5877)
  - X346 K835, undated; nos. 149-182, 27 catalogs
    - Old Settler Bookshop (R. Kolvoord); Walpole, New Hampshire (Box 915, Folder 5878)
    - Old Settler Bookshop (R. Kolvoord); Walpole, New Hampshire (Box 916, Folder 5879-5882)
  - X346 K86, 1936-1959; nos. 1-40, 40 catalogs
    - Nada Kramar; New York, N. Y. (Box 916, Folder 5883-5884)
    - Nada Kramar; New York, N. Y. (Box 917, Folder 5885-5887)
  - X346 K861, undated; nos. 1-33, 14 catalogs
    - Leon Kramer; New York, N. Y. (Box 917, Folder 5888-5889)
    - Leon Kramer; New York, N. Y. (Box 918, Folder 5890)
  - X346 K868, undated; nos. 1-169, 140 catalogs
    - H. P. Kraus; New York, N. Y. (Box 918, Folder 5891-5894)
    - H. P. Kraus; New York, N. Y. (Box 919, Folder 5895-5897)
    - H. P. Kraus; New York, N. Y. (Box 920, Folder 5898-5903)
    - H. P. Kraus; New York, N. Y. (Box 921, Folder 5904-5909)
    - H. P. Kraus; New York, N. Y. (Box 922, Folder 5910-5915)
    - H. P. Kraus; New York, N. Y. (Box 923, Folder 5916-5921)
    - H. P. Kraus; New York, N. Y. (Box 924, Folder 5922-5926)
    - H. P. Kraus; New York, N. Y. (Box 925, Folder 5927-5932)
    - H. P. Kraus; New York, N. Y. (Box 926, Folder 5933-5938)
    - H. P. Kraus; New York, N. Y. (Box 927, Folder 5939-5945)
    - H. P. Kraus; New York, N. Y. (Box 928, Folder 5946-5952)
    - H. P. Kraus; New York, N. Y. (Box 929, Folder 5953)
  - X346 K868 I, undated; nos. 1-375, 25 catalogs
    - H. P. Kraus; New York, N. Y. (Box 929, Folder 5954-5958)
    - H. P. Kraus; New York, N. Y. (Box 930, Folder 5959)
  - X346 K868 II, undated; nos. 1-84, 67 catalogs
    - H. P. Kraus; New York, N. Y. (Box 930, Folder 5960-5964)
    - H. P. Kraus; New York, N. Y. (Box 931, Folder 5965-5969)
    - H. P. Kraus; New York, N. Y. (Box 932, Folder 5970-5975)
    - H. P. Kraus; New York, N. Y. (Box 933, Folder 5976)
  - X346 K868 III, undated; nos. 6-206, 38 catalogs
    - H. P. Kraus; New York, N. Y. (Box 933, Folder 5977-5980)
    - H. P. Kraus; New York, N. Y. (Box 934, Folder 5981-5984)
    - H. P. Kraus; New York, N. Y. (Box 935, Folder 5985)
  - X346 K868 IV, undated; nos. 1-201, 15 catalogs
    - H. P. Kraus; New York, N. Y. (Box 935, Folder 5986-5987)
  - X346 K868 V, undated; nos. 6-9, 4 catalogs
    - H. P. Kraus; New York, N. Y. (Box 935, Folder 5988)
  - X346 K871, undated; nos. 43-53, 6 catalogs
    - Edgar Krebs; Chicago, Illinois (Box 935, Folder 5989)
  - X346 K8999, undated; nos. 1-12, 6 catalogs
    - P. S. Krivatsy; Washington, D.C. (Box 935, Folder 5990)
  - X346 K912, undated; unnumbered, 15 catalogs
    - Kroch's Bookstores, Inc; Chicago, IL (Box 936, Folder 5991-5993)
  - X346 K925, undated; nos. 55-102, 46 catalogs
    - Milton Kronovet; Brooklyn, N. Y. (Box 936, Folder 5994-5995)
  - X346 K9515, undated; nos. 3041-3502, 46 catalogs
    - Kubon Sagner; München (Box 937, Folder 5996-5999)
- L
  - X346 L115, 1815; unnumbered, 1 catalog
    - Lackington, Allen and Co.; [London] (Box 937, Folder 6000)
  - X346 L12, 1907 - 1911; nos. 1-20, 31 catalogs
    - Niel Morrow Ladd Company; Brooklyn, N. Y. (Box 938, Folder 6001-6002)
  - X346 L12 II, 1906-undated; nos. 1-7, 7 catalogs
    - Niel Morrow Ladd Company; Brooklyn, N. Y. (Box 938, Folder 6003)
  - X346 L1267, undated; no. 29, 1 catalog
    - Leonce Laget; Paris (Box 938, Folder 6004)
  - X346 L128, undated; nos. 400-478, 57 catalogs
    - Orientbuchhandlung Heinz Lafaire; Germany (Box 938, Folder 6004-6007)
  - X346 L132, 1962 - 1970; nos. 85-99, 9 catalogs
    - Louis Lafitte; Marseille (Box 939, Folder 6008-6009)
  - X346 L1321, 1971-1976, undated; nos. 1-91, 4 catalogs
    - Jeanne Lafitte; Marseille (Box 939, Folder 6010)
  - X346 L1367, undated, 1971-1986; nos. 6-65, 51 catalogs
    - Leonce Laget; Paris (Box 939, Folder 6011-6014)
    - Leonce Laget; Paris (Box 940, Folder 6015-6020)
    - Leonce Laget; Paris (Box 941, Folder 6021-6027)
    - Leonce Laget; Paris (Box 942, Folder 6028-6032)
    - Leonce Laget; Paris (Box 943, Folder 6033)
  - X346 L144, 1822; unnumbered, 1 catalog
    - Wm. D. Laing; Edinburgh (Box 943, Folder 6034)
  - X346 L148, 1938 - 1961; nos. 286-338, 13 bulletins
    - Lajouane; Buenos Aires (Box 943, Folder 6035-6036)
  - X346 L148 I, 1936 - 1948; unnumbered, 5 catalogs
    - Lajouane, J. Cia; Buenos Aires (Box 943, Folder 6037)
  - X346 L175, undated, 1931-1948; nos. 1-30, 29 catalogs
    - Chez Durtal, Pierre Lambert; Paris (Box 943, Folder 6038-6039)
    - Chez Durtal, Pierre Lambert; Paris (Box 944, Folder 6040-6041)
  - X346 L175 I, 1935; no. 1, 1 bulletin
    - Chez Durtal, Pierre Lambert; Paris (Box 944, Folder 6042)
  - X346 L183, undated; nos. 25-39, 6 catalogs
    - Lamesa Booksellers, Inc.; Lamesa, Texas (Box 944, Folder 6043)
  - X346 L255, undated; nos. 6-13:2, 6 catalogs
    - Herbert Lang Cie; Bern, Schweiz (Box 944, Folder 6044-6045)
  - X346 L255 I, 1949 - 1969; nos. 1-69, 12 catalogs
    - Herbert Lang Cie; Bern, Schweiz (Box 944, Folder 6046)
    - Herbert Lang Cie; Bern, Schweiz (Box 945, Folder 6047-6051)
  - X346 L255 II, undated; nos. 9-55, 9 catalogs
    - Herbert Lang Cie; Bern, Schweiz (Box 945, Folder 6052-6054)
    - Herbert Lang Cie; Bern, Schweiz (Box 946, Folder 6055-6056)
  - X346 L26, 1908 - 1938; nos. 1-65, 53 catalogs
    - Libreria Otto Lang; Firenze (Box 946, Folder 6057-6061)
    - Libreria Otto Lang; Firenze (Box 947, Folder 6062-6067)
  - X346 L26 I, 1932 - 1940; nos. 2-13, 10 lists
    - Otto Lang; Florence (Box 947, Folder 6068-6069)
  - X346 L262, 1952 - 1981; nos. 7-38, 5 catalogs
    - Lange, Maxwell Springer Ltd.; London (Box 948, Folder 6070)
  - X346 L262 I, 1951 - 1953; unnumbered, 8 catalogs
    - Lange, Maxwell Springer Ltd.; London (Box 948, Folder 6071-6072)
  - X346 L3225, 1951 - 1974; nos. 45-67, 8 catalogs
    - Lardanchet Librairie; Paris (Box 948, Folder 6073-6076)
    - Lardanchet Librairie; Paris (Box 949, Folder 6077-6079)
  - X346 L3235, undated; nos. 5-63, 37 catalogs
    - Lunge Larsen Antikvar; Oslo (Box 949, Folder 6080-6082)
    - Lunge Larsen Antikvar; Oslo (Box 950, Folder 6083-6086)
  - X346 L324, 1953 - 1958; unnumbered, 4 catalogs
    - Larson's; Hollywood, Calif. (Box 950, Folder 6087)
  - X346 L327, 1853 - 1858; nos. 14-24, 9 catalogs
    - Olive Lasbury; Bristol (Box 950, Folder 6088-6089)
  - X346 L33, 1910 - 1952; nos. 1-284, 196 catalogs
    - G.H. Last; Bromley, Kent (Box 950, Folder 6090)
    - G.H. Last; Bromley, Kent (Box 951, Folder 6091-6096)
    - G.H. Last; Bromley, Kent (Box 952, Folder 6097-6103)
    - G.H. Last; Bromley, Kent (Box 953, Folder 6104-6107)
  - X346 L3735, undated; nos. 51-60, 9 catalogs
    - Arthur Lauria; Paris (Box 953, Folder 6108-6109)
    - Arthur Lauria; Paris (Box 954, Folder 6110-6111)
  - X346 L3735 I, undated; unnumbered, 8 catalogs
    - Arthur Lauria; Paris (Box 954, Folder 6112-6115)
  - X346 L3825, 1964 - 1967; nos. 26-38, 7 catalogs
    - Camille Lavallee; Montreal, Que. (Box 955, Folder 6116-6117)
  - X346 L444 I, 1934 - 1986; nos. 104-228, 103 catalogs
    - E.M. Lawson Company; Sutton Coldfield (Box 955, Folder 6118-6122)
    - E.M. Lawson Company; Sutton Coldfield (Box 956, Folder 6123-6129)
    - E.M. Lawson Company; Sutton Coldfield (Box 957, Folder 6130-6133)
  - X346 L444 II, 1924 - 1928; nos. 6-48, 13 lists
    - E.M. Lawson Company; Sutton Coldfield (Box 957, Folder 6134)
  - X346 L452, 1818; unnumbered, 1 catalog
    - Jane Laycock Bookseller; London (Box 957, Folder 6135)
  - X346 L455, undated; nos. 1-77, 61 catalogs
    - A.W. Laywood; Knipton, Grantham, Lincolnshire (Box 958, Folder 6136-6142)
    - A.W. Laywood; Knipton, Grantham, Lincolnshire (Box 959, Folder 6143-6146)
  - X346 L46, 1825; unnumbered, 2 catalogs
    - H.C. Cary I. Lea; Philadelphia (Box 959, Folder 6147)
  - X346 L474, 1949-1973, undated; nos. 1-41, 39 catalogs
    Includes one list
    - Leamington Bok Shop; Washington, D. C. (Box 959, Folder 6148-6149)
    - Leamington Bok Shop; Washington, D. C. (Box 960, Folder 6150-6156)
    - Leamington Bok Shop; Washington, D. C. (Box 961, Folder 6157-6158)
  - X346 L487, 1967 - 1969; nos. 3-10, 8 catalogs
    - Lea Valley Books; Sussex, England (Box 961, Folder 6159)
  - X346 L489, 1868; unnumbered, 1 catalog
    - Leavitt, Strebeigh Co.; Clinton Hall, New York (Box 961, Folder 6160)
  - X346 L4965, 1904 - 1905; nos. 20-21, 2 catalogs
    - Librairie Henri Leclerc; [Paris] (Box 961, Folder 6161-6162)
  - X346 L499, 1930-1932, undated; nos. 3-19, 13 catalogs
    - Librairie Celto-Bretonne, Maurice Le Dault; Quimper (Box 961, Folder 6163-6165)
  - X346 L527, undated; nos. 1-33, 29 catalogs
    - Librairie Robert Legueltel; Paris (Box 962, Folder 6166-6169)
  - X346 L527 I, 1977; unnumbered, 1 catalog
    - Librairie Legueltel; Paris (Box 962, Folder 6170)
  - X346 L528, 1893; no. 6, 1 catalog
    - J. F. Lehmanns Medicinische Fachkataloge; Munich (Box 962, Folder 6171)
  - X346 L528 I, 1951 - 1964; unnumbered, 6 catalogs
    - J. F. Lehmanns Medizinische Buchandlung; Munich (Box 962, Folder 6172)
  - X346 L53 I, 1899-1916, undated; parts 1-12, new series nos. 1-31, 41 catalogs
    - J. J. Leighton Ltd.; London (Box 962, Folder 6173)
    - J. J. Leighton Ltd.; London (Box 963, Folder 6174-6180)
    - J. J. Leighton Ltd.; London (Box 964, Folder 6181-6187)
    - J. J. Leighton Ltd.; London (Box 965, Folder 6188-6191)
  - X346 L53 II, undated; nos. 5A-7A, B-E, unnumbered, 10 lists
    - J. J. Leighton Ltd.; London (Box 965, Folder 6192)
  - X346 L5382, undated; nos. 1-15, 13 catalogs
    - Pierre Lelant; Angers, France (Box 965, Folder 6193-6194)
  - X346 L5412, 1924 - 1935; nos. 1-31, 27 catalogs
    - Librairie P. Lemallier Fils; Strasbourg (Box 966, Folder 6195-6198)
  - X346 L5415, undated; nos. 58-247, 17 catalogs
    - Victor Lemasle; Paris (Box 966, Folder 6199-6201)
  - X346 L5424 I, 1930 - 1939; nos. 5-70, 59 catalogs
    - Th. Le Meur; Dijon (Box 966, Folder 6202-6203)
    - Th. Le Meur; Dijon (Box 967, Folder 6204-6207)
  - X346 L5562, 1820; unnumbered, 1 catalog
    - John Lepard; Strand, London (Box 967, Folder 6208)
  - X346 L5653 I, 1946, undated; nos. 1-239, 2 catalogs
    - N. T., Leslie; Hull, England (Box 967, Folder 6209)
  - X346 L5653 II, 1947 - 1950; nos. 1-38, 13 catalogs
    - N. T., Leslie; Hull, England (Box 967, Folder 6210-6211)
    - N. T., Leslie; Hull, England (Box 968, Folder 6212)
  - X346 L578 I, undated, 1941; unnumbered, 8 catalogs
    - Harry A. Levinson; New York (Box 968, Folder 6213)
    - Harry A. Levinson; New York (Box 968, Folder 6214)
  - X346 L578 II, 1943-1954, undated; nos. 16-62, 47 catalogs
    Location variant: Beverly Hills, California
    - Harry A. Levinson; New York (Box 968, Folder 6215-6219)
    - Harry A. Levinson; New York (Box 969, Folder 6220-6225)
    - Harry A. Levinson; New York (Box 970, Folder 6226-6230)
  - X346 L5783, undated; nos. 136-218, 21 catalogs
    - Jacques Levy; Paris (Box 970, Folder 6231-6232)
    - Jacques Levy; Paris (Box 971, Folder 6233-6234)
  - X346 L5785, undated; nos. 7-21, 11 catalogs
    - Irving Lew; New York, N. Y. (Box 971, Folder 6235)
  - X346 L585, 1923 - 1939; unnumbered, 33 catalogs
    - H. K. Lewis Co. Ltd.; London (Box 971, Folder 6236-6239)
    - H. K. Lewis Co. Ltd.; London (Box 972, Folder 6240)
  - X346 L585 I, 1939 - 1958; unnumbered, 3 catalogs
    - H. K. Lewis Co. Ltd.; London (Box 972, Folder 6241)
  - X346 L585 II, 1903 - 1939; unnumbered, nos. 165-223, 15 catalogs
    - H. K. Lewis Co. Ltd.; London (Box 972, Folder 6242)
  - X346 L5875, undated; nos. 1-30, 8 catalogs
    - Michael Lewis; Cardiff, U. K. (Box 972, Folder 6243-6244)
  - X346 L6154, 1913 - 1928; unnumbered, 76 catalogs
    - Librairie des Amateurs; Paris (Box 972, Folder 6245-6247)
    - Librairie des Amateurs; Paris (Box 973, Folder 6248-6250)
  - X346 L6155, undated; nos. 1-208, 14 catalogs
    - Librairie de L'Abbaye; Paris (Box 973, Folder 6251-6252)
  - X346 L6156, 1925 - 1957; nos. 9-74, 49 catalogs
    - Librairie Denis; Paris (Box 973, Folder 6253-6254)
    - Librairie Denis; Paris (Box 974, Folder 6255-6258)
  - X346 L61698, 1908 - 1923; unnumbered, 11 catalogs
    - Librairie Henri Saffroy; Paris (Box 974, Folder 6259-6262)
  - X346 L61719, 1952 - 1957; nos. 9-20, 9 catalogs
    - Librairie F. Janicot; Paris (Box 975, Folder 6263)
  - X346 L6175, 1951 - 1971; nos. 20-60, 27 catalogs
    - Librairie Leconte; Paris (Box 975, Folder 6264-6265)
  - X346 L6175 I, undated; nos. 10-24, 10 catalogs
    - Librairie Leconte; Paris (Box 975, Folder 6266)
  - X346 L6175 II, undated; nos. 1-52, 43 catalogs
    - Librairie Leconte; Paris (Box 975, Folder 6267-6269)
    - Librairie Leconte; Paris (Box 976, Folder 6270-6271)
  - X346 +L61761, undated; nos. 94-100, 4 catalogs
    - Librairie Lipton; New York, N. Y. (Box 976, Folder 6272)
  - X346 L617613, 1950 - 1963; unnumbered, 33 catalogs
    - Librairie Morin; Paris (Box 976, Folder 6273-6276)
  - X346 L61881, 1952 - 1977; nos. 13-101, 75 catalogs
    - Libreria "Rinascimento"; Roma (Box 977, Folder 6277-6284)
  - X346 L61881 I, 1952 - 1954; nos. 2-12, 7 catalogs
    - Libreria Turri; Milano (Box 978, Folder 6285)
  - X346 L618815, 1952 - 1965; unnumbered, 23 catalogs
    - Libreria Salimbeni; Firenze (Box 978, Folder 6286-6288)
  - X346 L61894, 1948 - 1952; nos. 23-61, 14 catalogs
    - Librairie Musicale; Bruxelles (Box 978, Folder 6289-6290)
    - Librairie Musicale; Bruxelles (Box 979, Folder 6301)
  - X346 L61818, 1938; nos. 77-78, 2 catalogs
    - Libreria Antiquaria Mediolanum; Milano (Box 978, Folder 6291)
  - X346 L61880, 1958 - 1959; nos., 83-91, 3 catalogs
    - Librerí Puvill; Barcelona (España) (Box 978, Folder 6292)
  - X346 L618193, 1952 - 1976; nos. 22-89, new series no. 14, 46 catalogs
    - Libreria Dante Ditta Oreste Gozzini; Firenze (Box 978, Folder 6293-6297)
    - Libreria Dante Ditta Oreste Gozzini; Firenze (Box 979, Folder 6298-6300)
  - X346 L61894 I, 1952 - 1955; unnumbered, 2 catalogs
    - Libreria Vinciana; Milano (Box 979, Folder 6302)
  - X346 L61894 II, 1953; nos. 1-2, 2 catalogs
    - Libreria Vinciana; Milano (Box 979, Folder 6303)
  - X346 L61894 III, 1963; nos. 2-3, 2 catalogs
    - Libreria Vinciana; Milano (Box 979, Folder 6304)
  - X346 L6193, undated; nos. 47-48, 2 catalogs
    - Libris London Ltd.; London (Box 980, Folder 6305)
  - X346 +L6193, undated; nos. 5-7, 3 catalogs
    - Libris London Ltd.; London (Box 980, Folder 6306)
  - X346 L632, undated, 1885-1960; nos. 1-360:2, 141 catalogs
    - Bernh. Liebisch; Leipzig (Box 980, Folder 6307-6312)
    - Bernh. Liebisch; Leipzig (Box 981, Folder 6313-6319)
    - Bernh. Liebisch; Leipzig (Box 982, Folder 6320-6326)
    - Bernh. Liebisch; Leipzig (Box 983, Folder 6327-6333)
    - Bernh. Liebisch; Leipzig (Box 984, Folder 6334-6339)
    - Bernh. Liebisch; Leipzig (Box 985, Folder 6340-6341)
  - X346 L632 I, 1929 - 1937; nos. 1-19, 15 catalogs
    - Antiquariat Bernh. Liebisch; Leipzig (Box 985, Folder 6342-6344)
  - X346 L632 II, 1930 - 1931; nos. 1-3, 2 catalogs
    - Antiquariat Bernh. Liebisch; Leipzig (Box 985, Folder 6345)
  - X346 L64 I, 1923 - 1954; nos. 1-25, 26 catalogs
    Name variant: R. A. T. Lier. Location variant: Firenze
    - R. Lier C.; Milano (Box 985, Folder 6346-6347)
    - R. Lier C.; Milano (Box 986, Folder 6348-6353)
    - R. Lier C.; Milano (Box 987, Folder 6354)
  - X346 L64 II, 1925 - 1938; nos. 1-22, 22 bulletins
    - R. Lier C.; Firenze (Box 987, Folder 6355-6358)
  - X346 L642, undated; nos. 48-50, 3 catalogs
    - S. Linden; London (Box 987, Folder 6359)
  - X346 L644, 1856 - 1864; unnumbered, 9 catalogs
    - Joseph Lilly; London (Box 987, Folder 6360-6361)
    - Joseph Lilly; London (Box 988, Folder 6362-6364)
  - X346 L645, undated; no. 79, 1 catalog
    - Limburger Antiquariat und Verlag; Limburg Lahn (Box 988, Folder 6365)
  - X346 L6483 I, undated; unnumbered, 1 catalog
    - Lincoln Book Shop; Chicago Ill. (Box 988, Folder 6366)
  - X346 L648, 1852 - 1858; unnumbered, nos. 86-149, 23 catalogs